{
    "subject": "resource/Famous_Studios",
    "predicate": "ontology/keyPerson",
    "object": "resource/Isadore_Sparber",
    "human_readable": "Isadore Sparber was a key person at Famous Studios.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9378699660301208,
            "question": "What role did Isadore Sparber play at Famous Studios?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9115890860557556,
            "question": "When did Isadore Sparber work at Famous Studios?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.883919358253479,
            "question": "What impact did Isadore Sparber have on Famous Studios?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8633860349655151,
            "question": "Why was Isadore Sparber important to Famous Studios?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8254071474075317,
            "question": "Who was Isadore Sparber?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5483797788619995,
            "question": "Was Isadore Sparber involved in animation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4831000864505768,
            "question": "Were there any other notable people who worked at Famous Studios?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4541272222995758,
            "question": "What was Famous Studios known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3451475501060486,
            "question": "What kind of work was done at Famous Studios?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26614874601364136,
            "question": "Did Famous Studios produce any famous cartoons?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Isadore Sparber was a key person at Famous Studios.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7301_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of work was done at Famous Studios?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7301_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Famous Studios known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7301_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any other notable people who worked at Famous Studios?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7301_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7301_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7301_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7301_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7301_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7301_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7301_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7301_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7301_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7301_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7301_63.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nIsadore Sparber is mentioned multiple times as working for and leading Famous Studios after the Paramount takeover in 1941.  He's credited as director and producer of cartoons there.  So the statement is supported by the documents."
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that Isadore Sparber was a key person at Famous Studios. Specifically, the documents mention his work with Fleischer Studios and its successor, Famous Studios, as well as his roles as director and producer of several cartoons produced by Famous Studios between 1941 and 1958."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}